export const BASEL = [
  {
    subjectScore: '0',
    isClose: false,
    image:
      'https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1657123766450-dd4fbdc99af6?q=80&w=1287&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D',
    subject:
      'The foundation of the city of Basel: legends and historical facts.',
    id: 'a1',
    levelQuestions: [
      {
        id: '1.1',
        question:
          'What legend is attributed to the founding of the city of Basel?',
        options: [
          'Roman emperor Augustus',
          'Celtic chief Basilisk',
          'Duke of Basel',
          'Italian merchant Basel',
        ],
        correct: 'Celtic chief Basilisk',
      },
      {
        id: '1.2',
        question:
          'What date is considered the official day of foundation of the city of Basel?',
        options: ['100 BC', '200 AD', '500 AD', '800 AD'],
        correct: '100 BC',
      },
      {
        id: '1.3',
        question: 'What river flows through the city of Basel?',
        options: ['Rhine', 'Danube', 'Hay', 'Thames'],
        correct: 'Rhine',
      },
      {
        id: '1.4',
        question: 'What does the coat of arms of the city of Basel symbolize?',
        options: ['Lion', 'Eagle', 'Bear', 'Dragon'],
        correct: 'Lion',
      },
      {
        id: '1.5',
        question:
          'What was the name of the first defense structure built in the city of Basel?',
        options: [
          'Fortress Margarita',
          'Castle Rudolph',
          'Fort Albert',
          'Martin Tower',
        ],
        correct: 'Martin Tower',
      },
      {
        id: '1.6',
        question: 'What was the origin of the name "Basel"?',
        options: [
          'From the Latin "Basilea"',
          'From the Greek "Basiliskos"',
          'From the French "BÃ¢le"',
          'From the Italian "Basile"',
        ],
        correct: 'From the Latin "Basilea"',
      },
      {
        id: '1.7',
        question:
          'When did the city of Basel get the status of an important trade center?',
        options: [
          'In the Middle Ages',
          'In antiquity',
          'In the Renaissance',
          'In the 19th century',
        ],
        correct: 'In the Middle Ages',
      },
      {
        id: '1.8',
        question:
          'What was the significance of Basel for cultural life in the Middle Ages?',
        options: [
          'Center of education and science',
          'Mecca for artists and poets',
          'Center of cultural exchange with other countries',
          'Place of large celebrations and festivals',
        ],
        correct: 'Mecca for artists and poets',
      },
      {
        id: '1.9',
        question:
          'What role in historical events did the mayor of Basel play in the first half of the 15th century?',
        options: [
          'Commander-in-chief of the army',
          'Conducted religious reforms',
          'Collected taxes and managed the municipality',
          'Represented the artistic elite of the city at royal receptions',
        ],
        correct: 'Collected taxes and managed the municipality',
      },
      {
        id: '1.10',
        question:
          'What was the significance of the Basel school for the development of science and art in the first half of the 16th century?',
        options: [
          'It was one of the central points of the Renaissance in Europe',
          'In the most prestigious school for the young aristocrats of Europe',
          'She contributed to the spread of humane philosophy in hideous countries',
          'She was the founder of new teaching methods',
        ],
        correct:
          'It was one of the central points of the Renaissance in Europe',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    subjectScore: '0',
    isClose: true,
    image:
      'https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1657123737634-a7bb19d4a6ba?q=80&w=1287&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D',
    subject: 'Basel in the Middle Ages: development of trade and culture.',
    id: 'a2',
    levelQuestions: [
      {
        id: '2.1',
        question: 'What activity did Basel prefer in the Middle Ages?',
        options: ['Trade', 'Agriculture', 'Crafts', 'Military affairs'],
        correct: 'Trade',
      },
      {
        id: '2.2',
        question: 'What was the role of Basel in the trade of medieval Europe?',
        options: [
          'Sea port',
          'Transit point on trade routes',
          'Center for the production of goods',
          'Trade union with other cities',
        ],
        correct: 'Transit point on trade routes',
      },
      {
        id: '2.3',
        question:
          'What architectural structure became a symbol of the cultural development of Basel in the Middle Ages?',
        options: ['Cathedral', 'Town Hall', 'Fountain', 'Castle'],
        correct: 'Cathedral',
      },
      {
        id: '2.4',
        question:
          'How did the cultural life of Basel influence the development of art in Europe?',
        options: [
          'Contributed to the emergence of new art schools',
          'Patronage supported',
          'Promoted new artistic movements',
          'All of the above',
        ],
        correct: 'All of the above',
      },
      {
        id: '2.5',
        question: 'How did Basel promote cultural exchange in the Middle Ages?',
        options: [
          'Organization of art festivals',
          'Translation and distribution of literary works',
          'Involvement of scientists and artists from all over the world',
          'All of the above',
        ],
        correct: 'All of the above',
      },
      {
        id: '2.6',
        question:
          'How did Basel contribute to the development of education in the Middle Ages?',
        options: [
          'Foundation of the university',
          'Organization of lectures and debates',
          'Distribution of books and manuscripts',
          'All of the above',
        ],
        correct: 'All of the above',
      },
      {
        id: '2.7',
        question:
          'How did Basel influence the development of architecture in the Middle Ages?',
        options: [
          'Having built huge defensive structures',
          'Combining elements of the Romanesque and Gothic styles',
          'Developing skill in wooden construction',
          'All of the above',
        ],
        correct: 'Combining elements of the Romanesque and Gothic styles',
      },
      {
        id: '2.8',
        question:
          'What was the main reason for the prosperity of trade in Basel in the Middle Ages?',
        options: [
          'Geographical position at the crossroads of trade routes',
          'A developed system of customs and taxes',
          'Services of intermediaries in trade transactions',
          'All of the above',
        ],
        correct: 'Geographical position at the crossroads of trade routes',
      },
      {
        id: '2.9',
        question:
          'How did Basel contribute to the development of art in the Middle Ages?',
        options: [
          'By holding art competitions and exhibitions',
          'By involving outstanding artists in their projects',
          'Forming architectural ensembles and sculptural compositions',
          'All of the above',
        ],
        correct: 'All of the above',
      },
      {
        id: '2.10',
        question:
          'How did Basel influence the development of book art in the Middle Ages?',
        options: [
          'Creation of book workshops',
          'Introduction of new printing technologies',
          'Distribution of manuscript samples throughout Europe',
          'All of the above',
        ],
        correct: 'All of the above',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    subjectScore: '0',
    isClose: true,
    image:
      'https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1657123754751-bb4b10d22709?q=80&w=1470&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D',
    subject:
      'Basel Reformation: the role of the city in religious transformations.',
    id: 'a3',
    levelQuestions: [
      {
        id: '3.1',
        question:
          'What is the role of the city of Basel in spreading the ideas of the Reformation?',
        options: [
          'The city was the center of the Protestant movement',
          'The city remained faithful to Catholicism',
          'The city was a place of strong religious conflict',
          'The city played a minor role in religious transformations',
        ],
        correct: 'The city was the center of the Protestant movement',
      },
      {
        id: '3.2',
        question:
          'What factors contributed to the spread of Reformation ideas in Basel?',
        options: [
          'The influence of prominent reformers who preached in the city',
          'Economic development and growing influence of the city',
          'Political changes that contributed to the introduction of the Reformation',
          'All of the above',
        ],
        correct: 'All of the above',
      },
      {
        id: '3.3',
        question:
          'How did the city of Basel participate in discussions about religious issues during the Reformation?',
        options: [
          'The city became a center of debate between reformers and Catholics',
          'The city remained outside religious conflicts',
          'The city actively participated in solving religious issues',
          'The city ignored religious discussions',
        ],
        correct:
          'The city became a center of debate between reformers and Catholics',
      },
      {
        id: '3.4',
        question:
          'How did Basel contribute to the spread of Reformation ideas in Europe?',
        options: [
          'The city publishing house printed and distributed the works of the reformers',
          'The city organized mass religious events and conferences',
          'Basel became the place of emancipation of women reformers',
          'All of the above',
        ],
        correct:
          'The city publishing house printed and distributed the works of the reformers',
      },
      {
        id: '3.5',
        question:
          'How did the inhabitants of Basel take part in religious transformations?',
        options: [
          'Actively supported reformist ideas',
          'Were divided between Reformed and Catholic views',
          'Opposed any religious changes',
          'All of the above',
        ],
        correct: 'Actively supported reformist ideas',
      },
      {
        id: '3.6',
        question:
          'How did the magistrate of the city of Basel influence the religious situation during the Reformation?',
        options: [
          'Adopted laws that affected the development of the Reformation',
          'Prohibited any changes in religious practices',
          'Tried to maintain a balance between the Reformed and Catholics',
          'All of the above',
        ],
        correct:
          'Tried to maintain a balance between the Reformed and Catholics',
      },
      {
        id: '3.7',
        question:
          'How did the Basel Reformation affect the cultural life of the city?',
        options: [
          'Contributed to the development of Latin literature and education',
          "It led to the decline of the city's cultural traditions",
          'Did not have a significant impact on the cultural life of Basel',
          'Stimulated the development of new cultural forms',
        ],
        correct:
          'Contributed to the development of Latin literature and education',
      },
      {
        id: '3.8',
        question:
          'What was the role of prominent personalities associated with the Basel Reformation?',
        options: [
          'They actively promoted the ideas of the Reformation within the city',
          'Became symbols of opposition to the religious status quo',
          'Influenced the formation of religious polemics and discussions',
          'All of the above',
        ],
        correct: 'All of the above',
      },
      {
        id: '3.9',
        question:
          "How did the Basel Reformation affect the city's economic condition?",
        options: [
          'Contributed to economic growth by attracting new investors',
          'It led to economic instability due to conflicts',
          'It did not significantly affect the economic condition of the city',
          'It led to the enrichment of elites and the deepening of social inequalities',
        ],
        correct: 'Contributed to economic growth by attracting new investors',
      },
      {
        id: '3.10',
        question:
          'How did Basel take part in the further spread of reformed ideas in Europe?',
        options: [
          'Became a center from which reformed principles spread',
          'Left behind in the development of the Reformation in comparison with other cities',
          'Lost its influence on the further spread of the Reformation',
          'All of the above',
        ],
        correct: 'Became a center from which reformed principles spread',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    subjectScore: '0',
    isClose: true,
    image:
      'https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1657123759472-247b4b1ef979?q=80&w=1287&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D',
    subject: 'Basel during the Renaissance: Influence on Art and Science.',
    id: 'a4',
    levelQuestions: [
      {
        id: '4.1',
        question:
          'What outstanding artists worked in the city of Basel during the Renaissance?',
        options: [
          'Hans Holbein the Younger',
          'Albrecht DÃ¼rer',
          'Leonardo da Vinci',
          'Michelangelo',
        ],
        correct: 'Hans Holbein the Younger',
      },
      {
        id: '4.2',
        question:
          'What is the role of the city of Basel in the spread of Renaissance architecture?',
        options: [
          'Development of the hotel business',
          'Construction of cathedrals and churches',
          'Creation of park complexes',
          'Construction of fortresses',
        ],
        correct: 'Construction of cathedrals and churches',
      },
      {
        id: '4.3',
        question:
          'What scientific achievements were associated with the city of Basel during the Renaissance?',
        options: [
          'Publication of the first scientific journals',
          'Development of new methods of treatment',
          'Studying astronomy and mathematics',
          'Invention of the first steamboat',
        ],
        correct: 'Publication of the first scientific journals',
      },
      {
        id: '4.4',
        question:
          'How did Basel publishers contribute to the development of science during the Renaissance?',
        options: [
          'Publication of scientific works and encyclopedias',
          'Dissemination of new inventions and discoveries',
          'Organization of scientific conferences and debates',
          'Funding of medical research',
        ],
        correct: 'Publication of scientific works and encyclopedias',
      },
      {
        id: '4.5',
        question:
          'How did the Basel School of Art influence the development of fine arts in Europe?',
        options: [
          'Preservation of traditional painting techniques',
          'Implementation of innovative styles and techniques',
          'Spreading the ideas of humanism through art',
          'Creation of the first museum of fine arts',
        ],
        correct: 'Spreading the ideas of humanism through art',
      },
      {
        id: '4.6',
        question:
          'How did scientific progress in Basel affect the development of medicine during the Renaissance?',
        options: [
          'Invention of new methods of treatment',
          'Study of anatomy and physiology of the human body',
          'Development of vaccines and drugs',
          'Organization of the first medical conferences',
        ],
        correct: 'Study of anatomy and physiology of the human body',
      },
      {
        id: '4.7',
        question:
          'How did Basel contribute to the development of culture and education in Europe during the Renaissance?',
        options: [
          'Foundation of a university and art academies',
          'Organization of cultural festivals and exhibitions',
          'Spread of book culture through publishing houses',
          'Promotion of the development of theatrical art',
        ],
        correct: 'Foundation of a university and art academies',
      },
      {
        id: '4.8',
        question:
          'How did the scientific community of Basel contribute to the exchange of knowledge and ideas in Europe during the Renaissance?',
        options: [
          'Organization of scientific conferences and seminars',
          'Publication of magazines and scientific works on various topics',
          'Inviting scientists from all over the world to lectures and discussions',
          'Formation of a network of scientific schools and laboratories',
        ],
        correct:
          'Publication of magazines and scientific works on various topics',
      },
      {
        id: '4.9',
        question:
          'How did the development of printing in Basel affect the spread of cultural values in Europe during the Renaissance?',
        options: [
          'Distribution of books and texts of classical literature',
          'Publication of maps and atlases for teaching geography',
          'Printing sheet music for distribution of musical works',
          'Production of decorative engravings to decorate books',
        ],
        correct: 'Distribution of books and texts of classical literature',
      },
      {
        id: '4.10',
        question:
          'How did the development of art in Basel influence the formation of new artistic trends in Europe during the Renaissance?',
        options: [
          'Creation of new styles in painting and sculpture',
          'Use of innovative technologies in the creation of art',
          'Propagation of the ideals of humanism through fine arts',
          'Promotion of the development of archaeological research through visual arts',
        ],
        correct: 'Creation of new styles in painting and sculpture',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    subjectScore: '0',
    isClose: true,
    image:
      'https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1710881861764-de1b599dd07e?q=80&w=1364&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D',
    subject:
      'Basel in the 19th and 20th Centuries: The Transformation of the City.',
    id: 'a5',
    levelQuestions: [
      {
        id: '5.1',
        question:
          'What industries transformed the city of Basel in the 19th and 20th centuries?',
        options: [
          'Textile and chemical',
          'Agriculture and fishing',
          'Metallurgical and automotive',
          'Forestry and woodworking',
        ],
        correct: 'Textile and chemical',
      },
      {
        id: '5.2',
        question:
          'What aspects of modernization affected the infrastructure of the city of Basel?',
        options: [
          'Development of the transport network',
          'Construction of new cultural buildings',
          'Reconstruction of historical monuments',
          'Expansion of green areas and parks',
        ],
        correct: 'Development of the transport network',
      },
      {
        id: '5.3',
        question:
          'What social consequences did the industrial revolution have for the inhabitants of Basel?',
        options: [
          'Rising standard of living',
          'Deterioration of working conditions',
          'Increasing the number of jobs',
          'Development of the social protection system',
        ],
        correct: 'Deterioration of working conditions',
      },
      {
        id: '5.4',
        question:
          'How did modernization affect the architectural landscape of the city of Basel?',
        options: [
          'Construction of tall skyscrapers',
          'Restoration of historical buildings',
          'Construction of industrial complexes',
          'Expansion of the network of streets and squares',
        ],
        correct: 'Restoration of historical buildings',
      },
      {
        id: '5.5',
        question: 'How did industrial development affect the economy of Basel?',
        options: [
          'Increase in the volume of exports',
          'Reducing the number of jobs',
          'Decrease in consumer activity of residents',
          'Increasing cultural tourism',
        ],
        correct: 'Increase in the volume of exports',
      },
      {
        id: '5.6',
        question:
          'What new technologies were introduced to the city of Basel thanks to industrial development?',
        options: [
          'Electrification of transport',
          'Production of cars',
          'Use of steam engines',
          'Development of computer technologies',
        ],
        correct: 'Electrification of transport',
      },
      {
        id: '5.7',
        question:
          'How did modernization affect the education and culture of Basel residents?',
        options: [
          'Expansion of the network of libraries and museums',
          'Reducing the availability of education',
          'Creation of new schools and university institutions',
          'Decreased interest in cultural events',
        ],
        correct: 'Expansion of the network of libraries and museums',
      },
      {
        id: '5.8',
        question:
          'How did industrial development affect the natural environment of the city of Basel?',
        options: [
          'Air and water pollution',
          'Preservation of ecologically clean zones',
          'Destruction of the landscape for the construction of factories',
          'Implementation of energy efficiency programs',
        ],
        correct: 'Air and water pollution',
      },
      {
        id: '5.9',
        question:
          'How did industrial development affect the medical industry in the city of Basel?',
        options: [
          'Development of new methods of treatment',
          'Reducing the availability of medical services',
          'Production of medical equipment',
          'Deterioration of the health of the population',
        ],
        correct: 'Production of medical equipment',
      },
      {
        id: '5.10',
        question:
          'How did modernization affect the socio-cultural life of Basel residents?',
        options: [
          'Expansion of cultural events and festivals',
          'Decrease of interest in cultural activities',
          'Deepening of religious conflicts',
          'Reduction of cultural diversity',
        ],
        correct: 'Expansion of cultural events and festivals',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    subjectScore: '0',
    isClose: true,
    image:
      'https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1710881862609-063176c44806?q=80&w=1365&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D',
    subject:
      'Basel Architecture: From Medieval Buildings to Modern Skyscrapers.',
    id: 'a6',
    levelQuestions: [
      {
        id: '6.1',
        question:
          'Which building in Basel is known for its medieval architectural style?',
        options: [
          'Basel Cathedral',
          'MÃ¼nsterplatz Town Hall',
          'Basel bridge',
          'University of Basel',
        ],
        correct: 'Basel Cathedral',
      },
      {
        id: '6.2',
        question:
          'What architectural style prevails in Basel during the Renaissance?',
        options: ['Gothic', 'Baroque', 'Classicism', 'Renaissance'],
        correct: 'Renaissance',
      },
      {
        id: '6.3',
        question:
          'Which building in Basel is famous for its luxurious baroque decoration?',
        options: [
          'Basel Cathedral',
          'MÃ¼nsterplatz Town Hall',
          'Basel bridge',
          'University of Basel',
        ],
        correct: 'MÃ¼nsterplatz Town Hall',
      },
      {
        id: '6.4',
        question:
          'What architectural style characterizes modern skyscrapers in Basel?',
        options: [
          'Functionalism',
          'Modernism',
          'Neoclassicism',
          'Postmodernism',
        ],
        correct: 'Modernism',
      },
      {
        id: '6.5',
        question:
          'Which building in Basel is famous for its tall Gothic tower?',
        options: [
          'Basel Cathedral',
          'MÃ¼nsterplatz Town Hall',
          'Basel bridge',
          'University of Basel',
        ],
        correct: 'Basel Cathedral',
      },
      {
        id: '6.6',
        question:
          'What architectural style characterizes medieval buildings in Basel?',
        options: ['Gothic', 'Baroque', 'Classicism', 'Renaissance'],
        correct: 'Gothic',
      },
      {
        id: '6.7',
        question:
          'Which building in Basel is famous for its majestic classical facade?',
        options: [
          'Basel Cathedral',
          'MÃ¼nsterplatz Town Hall',
          'Basel bridge',
          'University of Basel',
        ],
        correct: 'MÃ¼nsterplatz Town Hall',
      },
      {
        id: '6.8',
        question:
          'What architectural style characterizes buildings in Basel during modernism?',
        options: ['Functionalism', 'Gothic', 'Baroque', 'Renaissance'],
        correct: 'Functionalism',
      },
      {
        id: '6.9',
        question:
          'Which building in Basel is famous for its impressive modern design?',
        options: [
          'Basel Cathedral',
          'MÃ¼nsterplatz Town Hall',
          'Museum of Modern Art',
          'University of Basel',
        ],
        correct: 'Museum of Modern Art',
      },
      {
        id: '6.10',
        question:
          'What architectural style characterizes buildings in Basel during postmodernism?',
        options: ['Modernism', 'Gothic', 'Baroque', 'Functionalism'],
        correct: 'Functionalism',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    subjectScore: '0',
    isClose: true,
    image:
      'https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1665351118864-0c6b0c032704?q=80&w=1287&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D',
    subject: 'Basel Museums: From Art to Science.',
    id: 'a7',
    levelQuestions: [
      {
        id: '7.1',
        question:
          'Which museum in Basel is famous for its collection of works by Picasso and Hogarth?',
        options: [
          'Beyeler Foundation',
          'Tinto Museum',
          'Museum of Wasted Time',
          'Kunstgalerie Basel',
        ],
        correct: 'Beyeler Foundation',
      },
      {
        id: '7.2',
        question:
          'Which museum in Basel is famous for its collection of ancient art and ancient sculptures?',
        options: [
          'Basel Art Museum',
          'Museum of Wasted Time',
          'Basel National Museum',
          'Tinto Museum',
        ],
        correct: 'Basel Art Museum',
      },
      {
        id: '7.3',
        question:
          'Where in Basel can you see a huge collection of glass objects, ceramics and porcelain?',
        options: [
          'Beyeler Foundation',
          'Museum of Wasted Time',
          'Tinto Museum',
          'Globe Museum',
        ],
        correct: 'Beyeler Foundation',
      },
      {
        id: '7.4',
        question:
          'Which museum in Basel is famous for its collection of scientific exhibits, such as fossils and minerals?',
        options: [
          'Tinto Museum',
          'Basel National Museum',
          'Museum of Wasted Time',
          'Basel Museum of Natural History',
        ],
        correct: 'Basel Museum of Natural History',
      },
      {
        id: '7.5',
        question:
          'Where can you see the collection of masterpieces of Renaissance art and paintings by Rembrandt in Basel?',
        options: [
          'Kunstgalerie Basel',
          'Tinto Museum',
          'Beyeler Foundation',
          'Basel National Museum',
        ],
        correct: 'Kunstgalerie Basel',
      },
      {
        id: '7.6',
        question:
          'Which museum in Basel is famous for its collection of modern art and installations?',
        options: [
          'Tinto Museum',
          'Beyeler Foundation',
          'Kunstgalerie Basel',
          'Globe Museum',
        ],
        correct: 'Kunstgalerie Basel',
      },
      {
        id: '7.7',
        question:
          'Where can you see the collection of the history of technology and communications in Basel?',
        options: [
          'Museum of Wasted Time',
          'Basel National Museum',
          'Tinto Museum',
          'Globe Museum',
        ],
        correct: 'Museum of Wasted Time',
      },
      {
        id: '7.8',
        question:
          'Which museum in Basel specializes in the collection of archaeological finds and artifacts?',
        options: [
          'Basel National Museum',
          'Museum of Wasted Time',
          'Tinto Museum',
          'Globe Museum',
        ],
        correct: 'Basel National Museum',
      },
      {
        id: '7.9',
        question:
          'Where can you see the collection of modern art and exhibitions of contemporary artists in Basel?',
        options: [
          'Beyeler Foundation',
          'Kunstgalerie Basel',
          'Museum of Wasted Time',
          'Tinto Museum',
        ],
        correct: 'Kunstgalerie Basel',
      },
      {
        id: '7.10',
        question:
          'Which museum in Basel is famous for its collection of ancient Roman artifacts and mosaics?',
        options: [
          'Basel National Museum',
          'Tinto Museum',
          'Museum of Wasted Time',
          'Globe Museum',
        ],
        correct: 'Tinto Museum',
      },
    ],
  },
];
